[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The roots of Chinese astrology lay in the teachings of this ancient Chinese philosopher.", "correct_answer": "Confucius", "incorrect_answers": ["Mao Tse-tung", "Lao Tse", "Ho Shi Min"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most common reason for getting a massage?", "correct_answer": "Relaxation", "incorrect_answers": ["Joint pain", "Healing", "Back pain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pi is an issue of interest for mathematicians and math lovers from all over the world. In Japanese, what does the expression En syu ritsu refer to?", "correct_answer": "The Japanese term for pi", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitsubishis motto for the quest for finding better values of pi", "The largest computer in Japan used for finding even greater values for pi", "The Japanese term for an infinite number"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sarah Brightman, who became the first artist to hold #1 spots on the Billboard Classical and Dance charts simultaneously, has what type of singing voice?", "correct_answer": "Soprano", "incorrect_answers": ["Alto", "Contralto", "Mezzo Soprano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who hosted the 79th Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Ellen Degeneres", "incorrect_answers": ["Whoopi Goldberg", "Billy Crystal", "David Letterman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most popular sport among the people living in Brazil?", "correct_answer": "Football", "incorrect_answers": ["Volleyball", "Rugby", "Basketball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the origin of the popular feminine names Susanna, Susan, Sue, Suzie, Sanna?", "correct_answer": "Persian", "incorrect_answers": ["Greek", "Hebrew", "Old Germanic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which organelle makes up the cells translational apparatus that translates Messenger RNA (mRNA) into polypeptide chains?", "correct_answer": "Ribosome", "incorrect_answers": ["Lysosome", "Mitochondrion", "Golgi apparatus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the world\u2019s largest university for 2007 (considering total active enrollment.)", "correct_answer": "Allama Iqbal Open University", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ohio State University", "Indira Gandhi National Open University", "Islamic Azad University"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the occupation of the person after whom the human sideburns were named?", "correct_answer": "Soldier", "incorrect_answers": ["Aviator", "Painter", "Surgeon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the codename of the first US thermonuclear bomb test, carried out in 1954?", "correct_answer": "Castle Romeo", "incorrect_answers": ["Operation Chariot", "Operation Fat Man", "Operation Argus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Emmental cheese is known by this name in North America, Australia and New Zealand.", "correct_answer": "Swiss cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow cheese", "All of these", "Goats cheese"]}]